omnimedicalsearch.com 2010-06-20

# Privacy Policy - OmniMedicalSearch.com

**Overview**

OmniMedicalSearch.com has no interest, financial motivation or desire to compromise the privacy of our search users. 

OmniMedicalSearch.com does not collect personally identifiable information on any of it's users. Nor does it place cookies or information on your computer's hard drive with the exception of our BookMark option which adds our link to your Favorites Folder, or our search toolbar.

**Cookies & Web Beacons**

A cookie is a piece of data stored on the user’s computer tied to information about the user. Our website does not use cookies. However, Google Adsense, our Third Party advertising partner, may use cookies via our website. We have no access to or control over these cookies, once we have given permission for them to set cookies for advertising. 

The following discloses the information gathering and dissemination practices for this Web site. 

**Log Files**

Like most standard Web site servers we collect and use log files. This includes:

  * internet protocol (IP) addresses, 
  * browser type, 
  * internet service provider (ISP), 
  * referring/exit pages, 
  * platform type, 
  * date/time stamp, 
  * and number of clicks.

This is done to analyze trends, administer the site, track user’s movement in the aggregate, and gather broad demographic information for aggregate use. IP addresses, etc. are not linked to personally identifiable information. 

**Advertisers**

We use third-party advertising companies to serve ads when you visit our website. These companies may use information (not including your name, address, email address, or telephone number) about your visits to this and other websites in order to provide advertisements about goods and services of interest to you. If you would like more information about this practice and to know your choices about not having this information used by these companies, [click here](http://www.google.com/privacy_ads.html).

_The_[ _DoubleClick DART cookie_](http://www.doubleclick.com/privacy/faq.aspx) _is used by Google in the ads served on publisher websites displaying AdSense for content ads. When users visit an AdSense publisher's website and either view or click on an ad, a cookie may be dropped on that end user's browser. The data gathered from these cookies will be used to help AdSense publishers better serve and manage the ads on their site(s) and across the web._

**Aspects of the**[ **DoubleClick DART cookie**](http://www.doubleclick.com/privacy/faq.aspx) **: Include:**

* Google, as a third party vendor, uses cookies to serve ads on publisher's websites. 
* Google's use of the DART cookie enables it to serve ads to users based on their visit to OmniMedicalSearch.com and other sites on the Internet. 
* Users may opt out of the use of the DART cookie by visiting the [Google ad and content network privacy policy](http://www.google.com/privacy_ads.html). 

**Emails to OmniMedicalSearch.com**

If you contact OmniMedicalSearch.com, your email and all the information you list therein, will be kept on file. By contacting OmniMedicalSearch.com it is understood by you, the individual initiating contact, that you are volunteering to provide information about yourself and query in the contact email. All emails are confidential and will never be shared with Third Parties.

**Third Parties**

OmniMedicalSearch.com does not share your personally identifiable information with Third Parties, with the exception of Google Adsense, because we do not personally collect such information. 

**Search Engines, Websites and Links presented by OmniMedicalSearch.com**

OmniMedicalSearch.com is NOT RESPONSIBLE for the search engines and websites utilized in our search engines, Reference Desk, Conditions & Diseases, on our website. We have no control or influence over those websites. Those medical search engines and websites have their own Privacy Policy and Terms of Use for which OmniMedicalSearch.com is not responsible. You should view the Privacy Policy of the search engines and websites incorporated by our search engines if you have concerns.

**Our Mission**

Our goal is to present the user with a convenient, reliable and relevant search tool to find the best medical information possible. Best as defined by authority, relevance, date, non-commercial influence and variety. We are a information presentation service, NOT a user data and information collection website.   

| 

A Bottomside Toolbar compatible with all others.

Add the OMS   
Search Engine  
to Your Website

Got a suggestion or comment for us?  
Let us know

OmniMedicalSearch in the News

|    
---|---|---
